<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>विचारमञ्जरी (Vichāramañjarī)</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on विचारमञ्जरी (Vichāramañjarī)</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>One Peculiar Train Experience | The Job Human Trafficking Racket in India</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/hwh-to-bbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/hwh-to-bbs/</guid>
      <description>Background Where On a train, on the route: Howrah - Bangalore&#xA;When One fine August, 2024&#xA;What The train was 4 hours late, disrupting my day and giving me a stiff neck and back from sitting and waiting all day.&#xA;When I finally got up, it was even more painful on my berth, as more sitting awaited me among an equally tired crowd in the same predicament as myself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Short Note on CGPA | AKA | How To Approach College in India</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/cgpa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/cgpa/</guid>
      <description>Much is said about the importance of CGPA or its lack thereof to new students trying to navigate college life and to hopefully get a good job.&#xA;The popular belief nowadays is that CGPA does not matter and it&amp;rsquo;s only one&amp;rsquo;s skills, specifically coding skills, that matter during the recruitment process.&#xA;However, this is only half true. What was originally meant by this sentiment was that CGPA alone cannot get you a job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About विचारमञ्जरी</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to विचारमञ्जरी (Vichāramañjarī), a personal blog crafted by Karan Pratap Shaw and Divyanshu Kumar. This space is dedicated to exploring a myriad of topics, from the latest in technology to personal experiences and insights. Our aim is to provide valuable content that resonates with a diverse audience.&#xA;Our blog is powered by Hugo, a static site generator known for its efficiency and speed. We believe in the power of open-source, and our site is a testament to this philosophy, being built with a responsive design, easy content management, and customizable themes.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
